Adele One Night Only is a music, documentary film directed by Paul Dugdale.
A primetime special with performances from the superstar including Adele’s
first new material in six years plus her chart-topping hits.
The special will also feature an exclusive interview with Adele by Oprah Winfrey from
her rose garden, in Adele’s first televised wide-ranging conversation.
Self, played by Adele.
Self, played by Oprah Winfrey.
Self, played by Lizzo.
Self, played by Melissa McCarthy.
Self, played by Gabrielle Union.
Self, played by James Corden.
Adele One Night Only is a television special by English singer Adele.
The 88-minute program aired on CBS, and simulcast
on Paramount+, on 14 November 2021.
It features Adele's performances of previously unreleased songs from her fourth studio album, 30 (2021), as
well as material from her previous albums, interspersed with an interview with Oprah Winfrey.
The special drew favourable reviews from critics, who praised Adele's voice and performing skills and the
choice of the Griffith Observatory as the venue, but some criticised the interview segment.
It became the most-viewed entertainment special in the United
States since Oprah with Meghan and Harry (2021).
The special won five awards from five nominations at the 74th Primetime Creative Arts Emmy Awards, a Directors Guild of
America Award, and it earned a nomination for the Grammy Award for Best Music Film at the 65th ceremony.